Let's continue coding our content provider. Query will be
the most complex of the required content provider methods.
We begin with the bones of the query operation.
We use our SURI matcher object once again to
switch on the type of URI. This is the
only function where we will have to fill out
every type of URI in the content provider. Several
of them are used for querying only. We'll implement
the basic weather query first. For this query, we
just pass through all of the parameters to the
database. Pretty simple stuff. Let's fix these parameters so
they make some sense. So the strings here is
actually a projection. S is a selection. The next
array is selectionArgs. In the last string is sort
order that matches a lot better. At the bottom
of the function, we're going to set the notification
URI for our cursor to the one that was passed into the function.
This causes the cursor to register a content observer. To watch for changes that
happen to that URI and any of its descendents. By descendents
I mean any URI that begins with this path. But, we still need to test this.